Hey, how's it going guys?
Welcome back to another winning video ad breakdown tutorial where
I show you exactly the timeline and the sequence of a proven winning
ad that we have scaled, uh, in our creative agency.
Really excited about this one because this,
this particular ad took a lot of work to get to where it's at,
and that's kind of the process of creating content ads,
is continuously refining, learning from the data and improving,
you know, every second of the video until you can find a, a winning sequence,
a winning hook that actually resonates with the audience and one that you can
scale.
So there's a couple key things that I'll walk through in this video that were
like game changing, um,
realizations for us when creating this ad. And, um,
and hopefully, you know, you can,
you can get some value from that and apply into your own business.
So this product right here is actually a
incontinence leak proof period underwear. So, you know, I've,
I've worked with this brand for a very long time, um, and, you know,
they were drop shipping and then now they've kind of become a, an actual brand.
So, you know, over the years we've, we've done a lot of work to the,
to the website, to the product pages, to the offer.
We've got a lot of different pieces of content over the years as well. But, um,
when we shot this ad, um, it's kind of like a mashup of all of the different,
say, pieces of content that we've shopped for the brand over the years. Um,
and first and foremost,
the main thing that really stood out that really made this ad a
success was the hook. Okay? So the, I mean,
the scroll stopper as well as the headline.
So these are the two key things that really differentiated any
ad from the rest of the ads that we,
that we tested was how to prevent bladder leaks in public, how to
Prevent bladder leaks in public. A few,
This, this hook right here where she,
the actress is peeing herself, okay?
Because incontinence is about leaks.
We visually demonstrated leaks happening, and we tried different things.
We tried different angles, we tried pads, we tried tampons, we tried, um,
you know, other, other like comparisons. But the thing that really resonated,
the thing that took off was finding the winning visual hook
and that was leaking. Alright? And this is, this was,
so let me just
How to prevent bladder leaks in public a few
Months. And so let me just quickly go into the actual, like,
number of hooks that we have tested. Okay? So you can see all these,
these are all individual hooks. All right? So these are all, um,
visual hooks, and then these are all the actual headline hooks that we,
that we tested as well. So there's a lot, you know, we,
we test a lot of different hooks here, the same video for the most part,
but just different hooks. We also have the audio hooks down here too,
to match with the headline. So that's kind of the process that we use is,
you know, you got the headline,
the visual and the audio hook all happening at one time just to maximize
the attention and the scroll stop ability, that's even a word. So, yeah,
I'll move on to the rest of the video,
but I just wanna stress how important that hook really is and how big of a
difference it made for this campaign, for this, uh, and for this ad.
Let's move on to the, uh, the hook and the pain point public.
A few months back,
I discovered I had incontinence when I leaked in public for the first time, but,
Okay, perfect.
So our hook for this particular video was showing a
few a pain point shot, okay?
I can't believe one in four women have incontinence or leaked daily. This is,
we're just trying to create awareness around the problem, right?
We're not jumping straight into the solution yet.
A few months back I discovered I had incontinence when I leaked in public for
the first time.
Okay? So from an editing standpoint, there's a couple things I did here.
So, you know, adding emojis here,
there's some sort of visual cue that's grabbing your eyes
Few months back, I just,
Um, you know, I, we have a shot of her running up the stairs,
but I actually reversed the clip just to make it look a little different.
And then I added another emoji following her. I did a tracking shot, um,
just tracking her down the stairs, right? So it's just, you know,
we don't, we're not,
we're not a hundred percent sure what's happening yet in this video we're just
seeing kind of the visual cues. So that's keeping the curiosity loop open.
I discovered I had incontinence when I leaked in public for the first
Time. Okay? So here I added three call outs, um,
and an emoji. There's obviously another leak here,
but these are kind of those key words that the consumer is already thinking
in their mind.
So we want to kind of just like throw that in there as an opportunity to be
like, Hey, I, I know these things are embarrassing, I know it's uncontrollable,
uh, and I hate sayings, right? So these are the kinds of things that we're,
we're subconsciously throwing in there so that we can tap
into, you know, that decision later on.
But it wasn't until I found these leakproof panties that it changed everything.
So this was actually, uh, a shot from Billow. Uh,
we got U G C from Billow and you know,
she did a really good job kind of doing the cuts for us here and like kind of
the jump cuts. So I just used that clip as is and added, um,
added some titles there. So yeah,
basically right there we did the product introduction. Um,
now we do the product demonstration.
They're super comfy, fit my body really well,
and the high-waisted style shows off my curves. They're nothing.
So there we go. We did a benefit here, right? Product demonstration, comfy fit
My body really well, and the high-waisted style shows off.
We're highlighting really the key points to this product.
High-waisted fit shapes. My body feels like normal panties.
These are kind of the overarching patterns that the customer likes.
So we want to extract the best pieces of copy
into our, into our videos, right?
We don't wanna just like throw random stuff in there.
We want to really just focus on the things that matter.
My curves, they're nothing like those.
Um, this is another, this is another pain point, right?
We're we're driving that point home that, you know, using pads is, is,
is not the solution. So we added an extra pain point here.
They're nothing like those bulky
Render for a second. They're
Nothing like those bulky heavy pads, so you won't even,
So yeah, we're, we're showing the pain point. Then we're showing the solution
Bulky heavy pads. So you won't even notice the padded protection design com.
Okay? So we went from pain point to solution.
And here is a really important thing is we actually added a C T A
earlier on in the video.
So you can see like it's about like one third of the video and
I'm adding a C T A right here.
The reason being is sometimes people click through earlier, right?
We want to give people the opportunity to click a little bit sooner in any
video ad, especially after you've made an a strong argument.
And it's like they don't need to watch the rest of the video in order to know
what this product is and what that product solves.
There's gonna be people who watch the whole thing.
Those are the very interested people.
There's gonna be people who click on the first three seconds.
There's gonna be people who click somewhere in the middle.
You just wanna give an opportunity for everybody there.
So whether you're using a call out like I did here, like the c t a arrow,
um, or you use, you know, vocal, you,
you actually project it in the, in the speaking part,
whether it's like you're talking to camera or you have the U G C link.
So click now and, you know, visit the next page.
So you won't even notice the detection design comfort panties have.
All right, so here we're moving onto product benefits and features.
Reason number two
And comfort panties have three la
Let me just lower this a little bit so it doesn't lag.
Designed comfort panties have three layers of padded protection,
which helps prevent any accident. Dental leaks from soaking into my jeans. So,
no.
Okay, so here we go.
This was a very important demonstration where we showed the leak proof aspect.
This is like the second most valuable shot that we have besides
the leaking of the underwear, but showing that the,
the panties are actually leak proof was like a huge objection that
people have. They're like, oh, does it actually, you know, does it,
how much does it actually, uh, protect you against?
So we want to visually demonstrate that we've,
we visually demonstrated that as much as we could here for
Panties have three layers of padded protection,
which helps prevent any accidental leaks from soaking into my jeans.
So yeah, then we go, you know, we,
we showed that it protects it and then the benefit, right?
So it's almost like show the pain point, show the solution, show the pain point,
show the solution. That's kind of the pattern here,
Looking into my jeans.
So no more embarrassing moments in public or ruining my favorite clothes.
There we go again. We're, we're really drilling down. Hey,
this is the customer's new life.
This is what your life is gonna look like after wearing these panties. So
No more embarrassing moments in public or ruining my favorite clothes.
They also mask all odors, so you don't have to worry.
So let me just talk about this one really quick. Um,
My favorite clothes
After the pain point, we, we threw in a little additional feature,
honestly, like this probably could have been cut out to be honest.
'cause there's a lot of additional features, uh, and benefits to the underwear,
like, you know, machine washable, things like that. So, you know,
these aren't like a hundred percent, I would say as relevant.
So we put up further back into the video. They
Also mask all odors so you don't have to worry about running to the bathroom
right away. Design comfort panties are.
So here's the third reason, which is the washable and reusable,
Washable and reusable,
which saves you a lot of money compared to other alternatives out there.
So as you can tell, we had the c t a running the whole way through.
We just, you know,
at this point we are just trying to make the argument that this is a better
choice than what you're already doing. So if you're not sold yet,
you have the opportunity to continue watching it. If not, you know,
you probably have already clicked through or swipe past. These
Are washable and reusable,
which saves you a lot of money compared to other alternatives out there.
This was a very, um,
strong demonstration that I had shot of comparing the
actual cost to things, right?
So the more visual that you can be with your, with your ads,
with the content, with the raws that you shoot, you know, it's,
it makes such a huge difference in the final product. You know,
putting money together, um, showing visually, okay,
this is how much it's gonna cost you compared
To other alternatives out there.
Design comfort panties are designed to help women prevent surprise leaks while
feeling free in their own skin.
So here we're pretty much just reiterating some of the benefits here, um,
showing other women wearing the product and, you know, looking happy.
And there are over 60,000 raving customers that are wearing design comfort
panties every single day.
So yeah, this was more of a social proof, um, little overlay.
This is the ads or X one. Um, yeah,
we just wanted to highlight just how many women are using this product, right?
I think the more variety that you can show off in a, in a mashup in a video,
it just gives other people the, uh,
just the opportunity to kind of resonate with a a particular person.
It's 'cause you know, if you have one avatar in the entire video,
you could limit your reach and audience, um, you know,
in case in case you wanted to appeal to a different different type of person.
So it's nice to, to show different faces.
60,000 rating customers that are wearing design comfort panties every single
day. Everybody loves them. Try now for 30 days free.
Don't miss out on up to 50% off by tapping the link below.
Alright? So pretty much after that, you know,
I had a voiceover happening here,
but we could have added an actual U G C mashup of testimonials,
actual one-liners. So that would be another option here,
like I did in the Three Spirit video. Um, and then lastly,
we have the call to action showing the offer guarantee call to action
lifestyle image, just to kind of put everything in perspective here. Um,
and yeah, that's the whole video. So this, this thing was about, I forget,
probably like under a minute, under minute long. Um,
and so we got this voiceover done, uh, through Mic Monster,
which is, I use Mic Monster.
There's a lot of different voiceover options out there. Uh,
especially nowadays with ai, they're getting way, way better. Um, but, you know,
you, you drop your script in here and then you pick a voice and then pretty much
download the, uh, download the voiceover and plop it into your timeline. That's,
I, I know I have a different test, uh, different tutorial on that, uh,
further down the course. But this sequence right here,
it's very strong sequence. If you have a product that is a very, like,
visual pain point, that has a very visual pain point.
So showing before and afters that kind of thing is,
is this is a very strong sequence. So overall, I think,
you know, this is,
this is one video that we used as the base ad and
then iterated from here.
So we kind of took the same script and then changed the B rollout.
We changed the hook, um,
and kind of changed the music and just kind of kept that ad running for a
while. So that's one of the,
the beauties of finding and ruining ad is you can actually,
you can use that ad over and over again if it starts to die out.
You can change the hook.
You can change the first five to 15 seconds and it'll treat it like a completely
new ad,
but you want to base your next video iterations off
of the winning previous ones.
So until you find something that actually is,
is converting that actually resonates,
you still have to test until you find that, whether it's the headline,
whether it's the visual hook, whether it's the audio hook, you have to,
you have to nail those three combinations and from there then you can
recreate different looks. So I'll, I'll just kinda show you what I mean by that.
So from here, um,
I have this hook right here, but you know,
we shot different, different peeing hooks right here, there.
Leaks in public,
You know, this is a, this is another peeing hook. So
To prevent bladder leaks public,
I shot different variations of this because I knew that
How to prevent bladder leaks in public.
I knew that this, this is a, is a very strong hook.
Like let's shoot different variations of this over and over again.
Prevent bladder leaks in public. A few mugs when I leak in
Public for the, so that wraps up this tutorial. I hope you found value in this.
Um, this is a very fun one to do. Uh, if you guys have any questions,
just reach out and thank you so much for watching.